busbud.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy

Busbud Inc. values your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information of the users of the website www.busbud.com and the associated mobile application (together the " **Website** ") and the associated services (the " **Services** "). In this Privacy Policy, "Busbud", "we", "us" or "our" means Busbud Inc.

To better protect your privacy, we provide this Privacy Policy which explains how we collect, use, share and store your personal information, and how this personal information can be accessed and corrected when necessary.

Please read our Privacy Policy carefully before using the Website and/or Services. By visiting or accessing the Website, using our Services, contacting us or agreeing to receive emails from Busbud, you accept all the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If, at any time, you do not or cannot agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy, you must stop visiting or accessing the Website, using our Services and contacting us.

This Privacy Policy does not extend to websites operated by third parties. Busbud is therefore not liable for their privacy policies, procedures and practices. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use. As used in this policy, the terms "using" and "processing" information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization.

For the applicable terms and conditions governing access to and use of the Website including online purchase, please see the Terms of Use.

## INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

### 1\. What Information Do We Collect?

The types of personal and other information we may collect about you are primarily from four sources: (a) information you provide; (b) third party information collected; (c) information automatically collected; and (d) cookies. The legal bases for our processing of personal information are primarily that the processing is necessary for providing the Services and that the processing is carried out in our legitimate interests, which are further explained in the “How Do We Use Your Information” section. We may also process personal information upon your consent, asking for it as appropriate.

#### a) Information You Provide

Busbud collects personal information about you when you register to become a user of our Website and/or Services, and when you otherwise transmit such information to us via the Internet (including partner websites) or by email. For instance, and without limitation, to maintain your account we collect and store in a database your name, addresses, email address and telephone numbers.

#### b) Third Party Information Collected

Busbud collects personal information and other information about or related to you from Facebook and potentially other third parties (" **Facebook Information** ") when you connect, register or sign-up for the Services (including when you download the mobile application). In such cases, you allow Busbud to access and obtain personal information and other Facebook Information about you from Facebook (including from your Facebook profile information and pictures and information about your friends and likes) and such other third parties. The Facebook Information you allow Busbud to access and collect is affected by the privacy settings you establish with Facebook or such other third parties (and you can control and find out more about these settings by visiting [www.facebook.com](https://www.facebook.com/) or such settings of third parties, if applicable). The Facebook Information is subject to certain terms and conditions which restrict and proscribe our use, disclosure and protection of your Facebook Information in accordance with the applicable policies on [www.facebook.com](https://www.facebook.com/) (or the websites of such other third parties, if applicable) (the " **Facebook Restrictions** ").

#### c) Information Automatically Collected

Busbud automatically collects session information about your computer when you visit the Website. For example, we will collect your IP address, Web browser software (such as Firefox, Safari, Chrome or Internet Explorer), and referring website.

When you visit the Website, whether as a non-registered user just browsing, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (" **Log Data** "). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (" **IP** ") address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Website, pages of our Website that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Website, access times and dates, and other statistics.

We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Website and for the Website’s technical administration, to increase our Website’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor our Website to our visitors’ needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the Website meet the criteria required to process their requests. We do not treat Log Data as personal information or use it in association with other personal information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other non-identifying information.

#### d) Cookies

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Website. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Website, to better understand how you interact with the Website and to monitor aggregate usage by Busbud users and web traffic routing on the Website. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Website and then close your browser.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that they believe may be of interest to you, which are referred to as interest-based advertisements. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Website and/or Services. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having your information used by these companies, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

### 2\. How Do We Use Your Information?

We use the information that we collect in a variety of ways in providing the Services and operating our business, including:

  * to operate, maintain, enhance and provide all features of the Services, to provide the services and information that you request, to respond to comments and questions and to provide support to users of the Services;
  * to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our users, to improve the Services, and to develop new products, services, feature, and functionality;
  * to send you communications; or
  * to comply with legal and regulatory requirements, where applicable.

Internally, only employees who need access to your information for the execution of their duties will have access to it. Busbud may also share your personal information, including:

  * within the Busbud family of companies, which includes parents, corporate, affiliates, subsidiaries, business units and other companies that share common ownership;
  * with select business partners including bus companies that may communicate with you regarding your travel and their future special offers;
  * with third-party service providers working on behalf of Busbud;
  * to law enforcement authorities.

In the event of a change of ownership, sale, merger, liquidation, reorganization or acquisition of Busbud, in whole or in part, your information may be transferred as part of the transaction, as long as, the party acquiring such information agrees to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy.

When we disclose your personal information to third parties, we take reasonable measures to ensure that the rules set forth in this Privacy Policy are complied with and these third parties provide sufficient guarantees to implement appropriate technical and organizational measures.

### 4\. How Do We Store Your Information?

Your personal information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage third party service providers. By using the Services, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside your country of residence, which may have different data protection rules than in your country. While such information is outside of Canada, it is subject to the laws of the country in which it is held, and may be subject to disclosure to the governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies of such other country, pursuant to the laws of such country. However, our practices regarding your personal information will at all times continue to be governed by this Privacy Policy and, if applicable, we will comply with the _General Data Protection Regulation_ ("GDPR") requirements providing adequate protection for the transfer of personal information from the EU/EEA to third country.

Busbud has implemented various physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of personal information under our control. For instance, we limit access to your personal information to authorized Busbud personnel.

While we maintain a multitude of security measures to prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of your personal information, no security measures are absolute or wholly guaranteed. We will make reasonable attempts to notify you if we determine there were unauthorized acts by third parties that violate the law or this policy, or other security breaches, or where otherwise required by law.

Busbud will maintain your personal information for as long as a business need exists, or as required by applicable laws, regulations, or government orders.

We reserve the right to store personal information submitted by you at the time of making a Submission, including name, city, country and email. We store this information in order (i) to add your name to the contributor roll on the Website to thank you for your Submission and (ii) to notify you when the Submission is posted online, if applicable and if you have explicitly agreed in being notified. We do not spam. We will store your Submission with a timestamp.

### 5\. Rights Regarding Personal Information

On written request and subject to proof of identity, you may consult the personal information that we have disclosed, and ask that any necessary corrections be made, where applicable, as authorized or required by law.

However, to make sure that the personal information we maintain about you is accurate and up to date, please inform us immediately of any change in your personal information.

Under the GDPR, you may be entitled to additional rights, including: (i) the right to withdraw consent to processing where consent is the basis of processing; (ii) the right to access your personal information and certain other supplementary information, under certain conditions; (iii) the right to object to unlawful data processing, under certain conditions; (iv) the right to erasure of personal information about you, under certain conditions; (v) the right to demand that we restrict processing of your personal information, under certain conditions, if you believe we have exceeded the legitimate basis for processing, processing is no longer necessary, are processing, or believe your personal information is inaccurate; (vi) the right to data portability of personal information concerning you that you provided us in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format, under certain conditions; (vii) the right object to decisions being taken by automated means which produce legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affect you, under certain conditions; (viii) the right to lodge a complaint with data protection authorities. If you want to learn more about your rights under the GDPR, you can visit the European Commission’s page on Data Protection at: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/index_en.htm>.

### 6\. Update

Our Privacy Policy may be periodically amended without notice to reflect changes made to our practices. We therefore invite you to consult our Website from time to time to stay informed of the latest developments. Your continued visit or access of this Website, use of the Services or contacting us signifies your acceptance of the updated or modified Privacy Policy. If we modify it, we will update the "Last Updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. By continuing to access or use the Website, you are indicating that you agree to be bound by the modified the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the modified Privacy Policy you must stop visiting or accessing the Website, using our Services and contacting us.

### 7\. Children's Privacy

If you live in a country in the EU/EEA, you must be at least 16 years old to use our Services or such greater age required in your country to register for or use our Services. If you live in any other country except those in the EU/EEA, you must be at least 13 years old to use our Services or such greater age required in your country to register for or use our Services. In addition to being of the minimum required age to use our Services under applicable law, if you are not old enough to have authority to agree to our Privacy Policy in your country, your parent or guardian must agree to our Privacy Policy on your behalf. If you have any concerns about your child’s personal information, please contact us at [privacy@busbud.com](mailto:privacy@busbud.com).

### 8\. Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or your personal information, to make an access or correction request, to exercise any applicable rights, to make a complaint, or to obtain information about our policies and practices with respect to any service providers outside Canada, our Privacy Officer (or Data Protection Officer) can be reached by email at: [privacy@busbud.com](mailto:privacy@busbud.com).

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 25th, 2018.
